Timur Mukhamedov

SOFTWARE ENGINEER

Details

New York City United States 347-679-9994

tmukhamedov97@gmail.com

Links

LinkedIn

Github

Portfolio

Skills

Node.js

Git

Python

ES₆

CSS3

HTML5

React

MongoDB

PostgresSQL

Next.js

Express

Languages

English

Russian

Profile

Aspiring software engineer specializing in web development for the past year. My objective is to demonstrate my skill in building scalable, front-end applications with React Library and gain knowledge from more experienced developers in creating user-friendly experiences for people all over the world. I have built numerous web projects ranging from Blogs, Movie Search API, Portfolio and E-Commerce esque applications.

Working as an agent for the past three years, I have managed and assisted countless of clients, who are now close friends, on obtaining their dream homes for the best price on the market. It allowed me to expand my soft skills when working with various of people of many different ethnicity, while producing \$10,000 sales/month to Nest Seekers International with our team.

Working at VONN Lighting was an eye opening experience since it was a startup company. It required me to perform many different tasks in different departments at a fast pace, since the company consisted of five. During 2017-2018, our small team managed to improve sales by 30% as well as reducing return products by 10% with improved quality control.

Employment History

Real Estate Agent, Nest Seekers International, New York City

JUNE 2019 - PRESENT

- Assisted clients and real estate professionals in resolving clearance of all files prior to closing.
- Worked with a team that successfully closes an average of 10 deals per month.
- Provided excellent customer service for seller, buyer and renter leads.
- Worked with numerous landlords all over New York City through exclusive listings.
- Maintained property listings and handled all client correspondence.

Web Administrator, VONN Lighting, New York City/Miami

JUNE 2016 - JUNE 2019

- Monitored VONN web application and provided feedback with more potential website features.
- Made sure web application provided smooth user experience pre/post deployment.
- Managed to increase sales by 30% in the first year of working with company's team of 5.
- Managed web application help desk as well as processed orders via SAP Enterprise Resource Planning software.
- Controlled incoming data from engineering team and updated web application with necessary data.
- Every week conducted web scrapes on our partnered vendors (Wayfair, Build.com, Amazon, HomeDepot) for MSRP product price changes.
- Also managed product warehouse maintenance with our partnered warehouse vendor in Salt Like City, UT.
- Also processed returned products and checked for defective parts before resale.
- Also was lead customer service specialist for the company.

Education

Psychology, Queens College CUNY, New York City

AUGUST 2012 - JULY 2016

Graduated with Bachelors